this code is an example of an
infinite loop when i run the code i can
see that this loop just keeps going
there's nothing in our code telling the
loop when to stop and if you encounter
an infinite loop like this you can exit
the program by hitting ctrl c
[Music]
so in this particular problem what we
want to do
is iterate through the loop one time
and i'll put the string just keep
printing then
exit the loop with a simple loop like
this where you don't have
any condition telling the loop when to
stop iterating
we can use the reserved word break
so if i place break on line three of our
code
our loop will begin to iterate output
the string
and when it executes line three
the loop will be exited
so when i run the code i can see that
that's exactly what happens
if i put the break on line two
prior to outputting the string you can
see that our code will have no
output
and that's because when a break is
executed the block is exited immediately
not after the current iteration
so in order for our code to work as
expected we need to make sure to place
that break
after our call to put us
you